PAIGE BOYD PRODUCT DESIGNER (UX/UI)

www.paigeboyd.co.uk

PROFILE

I am a self motivated, enthusiastic and ambitious Product Designer.

I design intuitive digital products with a focus on creating a meaningful user experience. I enjoy getting involved in every stage of the Product Design process, and always strive to learn new skills to better myself as a designer.



EXPERIENCE

Product Designer

Dubai, UAE

Belfast, NI

Synechron

Dec 2021 - Present

Dec 2020 - Dec 2020

I facilitate key stakeholder meetings, discovery workshops and user interviews with users. Working across the entire UX/UI process from ideation and user research to wireframing and prototyping for Tier 1 banks and Fintechs, including Citi, HSBC and First Abu Dhabi Bank (FAB).

UX/UI Designer

Relative Ltd

Portadown, NI

June 2019 - Dec 2020

I designed software for companies globally, ranging from simple mobile and web apps, to large, scalable systems. I worked across the full UI/UX design process, as well as designing company promotional materials and websites.

Product Designer Paige Boyd Designs Ltd
Remote Aug 2018 - Oct 2020

Worked with clients across multiple industries to design websites, apps and platforms that align business needs with needs of customers.

Clients included:

Danske Bank, Finmondo, Funds-Axis, TapSOS, Assistant.ly, Relative, CheckaTrade.

Content Designer Intern

Belfast, NI

Sept 2016 - July 2017

EDUCATION

BDes (Hons) Interaction Design Ulster University, Belfast School of Art September 2014 - July 2018

Award: First Class Honours and Diploma in Professional Practice with Commendation. Deans List in Years 1,2 & 4.

Modules: Interaction Design, Designing with Content, UX & UI, Narrative & Storytelling, Dissertation Writing, Major Project Prototyping.



ACHIEVEMENTS

UI Design for Successful Software July 2020

Certificate awarded by the Interaction Design Foundation (IDF) after successfully passing the course and assignments

Deloitte Digital Experience AwardJune 2018

The Deloitte Digital Experience Award recognises outstanding skill and creative thinking in Interaction Design. Awarded for: Signar (degree major project).

EDGE Award (Ulster University)June 2018



MY TOOLKIT

Figma InVision
Adobe XD Pen & Paper
Adobe Illustrator Miro

Sketch Basic HTML & CSS



CONTACT

Email: paigeboyd1@gmail.com Whatsapp: +971 588536479

References available on request.



